<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<game>
	<title>Gummy Pop</title>
	<release-date></release-date>
	<website>http://www.playgummypop.com/</website>
	<press-can-request-copy>TRUE</press-can-request-copy>

	<platforms>
		<platform>
			<name>Apple App Store</name>
			<link>https://itunes.apple.com/in/app/gummy-pop/id1021924332</link>
		</platform>
		<platform>
			<name>Google Play Store</name>
			<link>https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.hashcube.bubble</link>
		</platform>
		<platform>
			<name>Amazon App Store</name>
			<link>https://www.amazon.com/hashcube-inc-Gummy-Pop/dp/B01G8KDY8A</link>
		</platform>
	</platforms>
	
	<prices>
	</prices>

	<description>STOP MATCHING and START POPPING! Pop the adorable GUMMIES to create incredible Chain Reactions!
  
	Download Now and enjoy the crazy chain reactions, super-fun power-ups, amazing level variations and incredible popping fun across hundreds of poptastic levels!
  </description>
	
	<history></history>

	<features>
	<feature>Unique and Exciting Chain Reaction Mechanic: An interesting new take on chain reaction mechanic: Grow Gummies - Pop Gummies - Create amazing chain reactions.</feature>
	<feature>Amazing Power Ups to help you in sticky situations: 9 awesome powerups to choose from, select the powerup that suits your gameplay style.</feature>
	<feature>Adorable Characters that you'll love: Four different gummies that grow from the sleepy Green gummy to the active Red gummy.</feature>
	<feature>5 distinct game variations: Never run out of fun with 5 different game variations. Keep an eye out for the interesting challenges.</feature>
	280 Challenging Levels: Play all 280 levels along your journey across 5 different worlds. 
	<feature>Deceptively Simple and Incredibly Fun Gameplay : Strategize to form clusters of red gummies, the bigger the clusters, the better the Chain reactions</feature>
	<feature>Captivating Music and Sound: Enjoy your journey across the mystery lands with awesome music to keep you entertained.</feature>
	<feature>Compete with friends for high scores : Challenge your friends, beat them by saving more gummies, compete on global leaderboards and be the Poppin’ champ.</feature>
	<feature>Play across multiple devices without losing progress: Sync with facebook and save your progress across all platforms, including Android, iOS and Amazon.</feature>
	</features>
	
	<trailers>
		<trailer>
			<name>Trailer</name>
			<youtube>Wa26b9gIqYE</youtube>
		</trailer>
	</trailers>
	
	<awards>
	</awards>
	
	<press>
	</press>
	
	<additionals>
	</additionals>
	
	<credits>
	</credits>
</game>
